当我们决定在这个百花齐放的世俗社会
When we decided to take on inner life issues
背景下处理内在生命问题时，
in the context of this fleur allistic secular society,
我们必须非常仔细地思考
we had to think very carefully about the metaphors
我们想要用来邀请人们进入
that we wanted to use to invite people
本质上是灵性旅程的隐喻。
into what is essentially a spiritual journey.
因为我们希望这些隐喻
Because we wanted those metaphors
是开放和慷慨的，
to be open and generous,
尊重所有的传统，
respectful of all traditions and
以及那些没有传统的人。
of people who have no tradition.
但与此同时，这些隐喻会
But at the same time metaphors that
会唤起我们对困难和充满希望的问题的注意。
would call our attention to difficult and hopeful questions.
我感到非常幸运的是，
And I feel very blessed really in the fact
我们偶然发现了季节性的隐喻，
that we sort of stumbled across the
作为实现这一目标的方法，
seasonal metaphors as ways to do that
它们为我们提供了非常好的服务。
and they have served us remarkably well.
我们使用的主题是四季的主题,
The themes we use are the themes of the Four Seasons,
也就是四季的隐喻。
the metaphors of the Four Seasons.
我们从秋天开始，基本主题
We start in the fall where the fundamental theme
是真实自我的种子。
is the seed of true self.
秋天是大自然播种的季节。
The fall is when nature is planting her seeds.
因此，我们邀请人们思考，
And so we invite people to think about
你出生时种下了什么种子,
what seed was planted when you were born,
你与生俱来的天赋是什么，
what are those birthright gifts,
你最初的自性是什么?
what is that original selfhood that you arrived with.
30、40、50年后的今天，你可能与之有一些距离。
now 30 40 50 years later you may be some distance from.
让我们回到过去，
Let's go back and
并 试着回想并重拾那颗种子。
try to recall and reclaim that seed.
当然，在冬天，这些种子会被埋起来，
In the winter of course those seeds are buried
感觉它们已经死了和消失了。
and it feels like they're dead and gone.
但事实是，在冬天,
But the truth is that in winter,
地下有很多事情发生，
there's a lot happening underground
正在等待着重生的季节。
that is awaiting a season of rebirth.
因此，我们在冬天问的问题
So the questions we ask in the winter
与死亡和垂死、
have to do with death and dying,
以及休眠和更新有关。
dormancy and renewal.
这是一个令人着迷的内在生活问题，
And it's a fascinating inner life questioning that
在我身上感觉死亡或垂死的东西，
which feels dead or dying in me is
它实际上进入了一个休眠期，
it in fact going into a period of dormancy
等待重生的季节。
and awaiting a season of rebirth.
教师们在面对
And teachers have found the most wonderful
他们内心的休眠时
things in coming to terms with what is
发现了最奇妙的事情，
dormant  inside of them,
奇妙的是他们现在能够
wonderful in the sense that they're now able to
用全新的目光看待他们的学生，
look at their students through new eyes,
因为作为一个青少年，除了一群门卫。
because what is a teenager but a bundle of doormen sees.
在春天，我们使用的
In the spring the theme
主题是悖论之花，
we uses the flowering of paradox
即在春天发生的事情是完全矛盾的，
that is what happens in spring is utterly paradoxical
从那似乎冻结和死亡的东西中，
that out of that which seemed frozen and dead,
有新生命在涌现中。
there is this proliferation of new life.
这非常... 但它本身就很矛盾,
And it's very... but itself is very paradoxical,
因为在春天变得美丽之前，
because spring before it gets beautiful
到处充斥着丑陋的泥土和淤泥。
is just plug ugly it's mud and muck.
我们都试图让它远离
And we're all trying to keep it off
我们的鞋子和房子，
our shoes and out of the houses,
除了泥巴和淤泥
but the mud and the muck
在美的产生过程中扮演着重要的作用。
have a role to play in the generation of beauty.
这种幽默也是关于谦逊的。
It's that houmous which is also about humility.
那是花儿生长的土地。
That is the ground in which the flower grows.
到了夏天,
And then in the summer,
我们谈到丰收和收获的季节，
we speak about the season of abundance and harvest,
所以现在的问题是，
so the question now becomes
在我的生活中，
what is it that is growing abundantly in my life,
在这个漫长的秋、冬、春的旅程中，
out of this long journey through fall, winter and spring,
有什么东西是丰收的和收获的，
that is meant to be harvested
是要为别人服务的。
to serve to feed others.
所以我们发现，
So we have we've discovered that
这些季节性的主题和隐喻
these seasonal themes and metaphors
可以为许多不同传统的人
can create the most generous room
和没有传统的人
for people of many different traditions and
创造最慷慨的空间，
no tradition at all to deal with
来处理内心生活的真正问题。
real issues of the inner life,
以一种不冒犯他们
to do so in a language that doesn't  offend them
或不排挤他们的语言来这样做，
or doesn't marginalize them and
并最终允许他们进入这种语言,
eventually allows them to come into the language,
对他们来说最有意义的语言。
their own language that has most meaning for them.
这是一个非常神奇的方式，
It's a very amazing way
可以浮现内心深处的人生课题，
to come out deep inner life issues
让人们专注于重要的事情。
keeping people focused on things that matter.
但与此同时，以一种每个人都觉得
And yet at the same time doing that in a way
在他们的特定传统中
that everyone feels honored
受到尊重的方式来做这件事。
by in their particular tradition.